A Finding Aid to the Fidel Danieli papers, 1962-1987, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Fidel Danieli papers
1962-1987
Archives of American Art
Danieli, Fidel
AAA.danifide
Archival Resource Key
8.4 Linear feet
The papers of Los Angeles art critic and writer, art historian, professor, collector, and artist Fidel Danieli (1938-1988) measure 8.4 linear feet and date from 1962 to 1987. Found within the papers are writing and research files, and 108 sound recordings of interviews with or about 45 Los Angeles artists conducted by Danieli in 1974-1975 for the U.C.L.A. oral history project "L.A. Community Artists." There are also sound recordings of art performances and art talks, and printed materials, including numerous exhibition announcements.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 3 series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Writing and Research Files, 1962-1987 (3.2 linear feet; Boxes 1-4)
Series 2: Los Angeles Artist Interviews and Performances, 1974-1975 (3.1 linear feet; Boxes 4-7)
Series 3: Printed Material, 1969-1985 (2.1 linear feet; Boxes 7-9)
Biographical / Historical
Fidel Danieli (1938-1988) was an art critic and writer, art historian, educator, and artist based in Los Angeles, California. Danieli received his B.A. in 1960 and M.A. in 1965 from the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA). For nearly 22 years, he taught at the Los Angeles Valley College in Van Nuys. He also taught and lectured at the California State College in Los Angeles and San Fernando Valley State College in Northridge.
Danieli was perhaps best known for his work as an art critic and writer, notably his reviews for Artforum from 1963-1968 that brought national recognition to many modern Southern California artists, such as Billy Al Bengston, Bruce Nauman, Robert Graham, and George Herms. Danieli was a member of the editorial committee of the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art's (LAICA) Journal, a contributing editor to Artweek, and writer and reviewer for ArtScene and Images and Issues.
Danieli's special interest was in the early Los Angeles Modernists and he received a National Endowment for the Humanities grant around 1974 to fund research on the subject. From 1974-1975, he was also an interviewer for the UCLA oral history project "Los Angeles Art Community." The project culminated in the 1974 exhibition Nine Senior Southern California Painters at LAICA.
Danieli was also a painter, sculptor, and collector. His extensive art collection included photographs, paintings, ceramics, and prints. He bequeathed the bulk of his collection to the Oakland Museum and the Los Angeles Museum of Contemporary Art (MOCA), and a few private collectors who were friends. His art library was donated to Los Angeles Valley College.
He was briefly married to Edie Ellis though they later separated. He suffered ill health for several years and passed away in North Hollywood on March 26, 1988, at the age of 49.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice. Contact Reference Services for more information.
Existence and Location of Copies
A few of the sound recordings in this collection have been copied for research access and are available in the Archives of American Art offices.
Scope and Contents
The papers of Los Angeles art critic and writer, art historian, professor, collector, and artist Fidel Danieli (1938-1988) measure 8.4 linear feet and date from 1962 to 1987. Found within the papers are writing and research files, and 108 sound recordings of interviews with or about 45 Los Angeles artists conducted by Danieli in 1974-1975 for the U.C.L.A. oral history project "L.A. Community Artists." There are also sound recordings of art performances and art talks, and printed materials, including numerous exhibition announcements.
Writing and research files consist of articles and reviews written by Fidel Danieli and supporting documentation and printed material. Files cover individual artists, exhibitions, and other scattered topics. Files on reviews of artists Danieli wrote include typescripts and handwritten drafts, printed materials, and photographs. Artists covered include Carlos Almarez, Larry Bell, Wallace Berman, Lorser Feitelson, Dan Flavin, Robert Graham, Jules Langsner, Richard Pettibone, Rachel Rosenthal, Alexis Smith, and John White, among many others. The file for Richard Pettibone includes 2 original sound cassettes and duplicates. Writings for exhibition catalogs and reviews of exhibitions focus primarily on Los Angeles area exhibitions or exhibitions of California artists. These files include notes, typescripts, and printed materials. Also found are files for magazine articles written by Danieli. Research files include a set of index cards documenting a chronology of Los Angeles art and 9 sound cassettes of television shows that focus on California art.
Interviews of and performances by Los Angeles comprise 108 sound cassettes. The majority of the cassettes are artist interviews conducted by Danieli in 1974-1975 for the U.C.L.A. oral history project "L.A. Community Artists," but there are also scattered recordings of art talks, panel discussions, and performances. Artists include David Antin, Eleanor Antin, Judith Bettelheim, Nick Brigante, Annita Delano, Allan Kaprow, Peter Krasnow, Peter Plagens, Gary Lloyd, John McLaughlin, Shirley Pettibone, Betye Saar, and John White, among many others.
Printed material consists primarily of exhibition announcements about California artists and exhibitions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Fidel Danieli papers were donated to the Archives of American Art in 1990 by Sage Stormcreek, executor of Danieli's estate.
Authors -- California -- Los Angeles; Art historians -- California -- Los Angeles; Educators -- California -- Los Angeles; Sound recordings; Photographs; Art critics -- California -- Los Angeles; Art -- Collectors and collecting -- California -- Los Angeles; Painting, Modern -- 20th century -- California -- Los Angeles; Interviews; Saar, Betye; Rosenthal, Rachel, 1926-; Smith, Alexis, 1921-1993; Pettibone, Richard, 1938-; McLaughlin, John, 1898-; Plagens, Peter; Pettibone, Shirley; Krasnow, Peter, 1886-1979; Almaraz, Carlos; Lloyd, Gary, 1943-; Langsner, Jules, 1911-1967; Bell, Larry, 1939-; Antin, David; Antin, Eleanor; Feitelson, Lorser, 1898-1978; Delano, Annita, 1894-; Berman, Wallace, 1926-1976; Brigante, Nicholas P., 1895-1989; Bettelheim, Judith, 1944-; Kaprow, Allan; Graham, Robert, 1938-; Flavin, Dan, 1933-
- Writing and Research Files, 1962-1987; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 3.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-4
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of reviews and articles written by Danieli, as well as supporting documentation and notes. Also found are Danieli's research files on artists and exhibitions.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as 3 subseries.
  Missing Title
  1.1: Artists, 1964-1987
  1.2: Exhibitions, 1962-1986
  1.3: Other Subjects, circa 1970-1986
  - Artists, 1964-1987; 1.1; Archival Resource Key
    Artist files include handwritten and typed drafts of writings about artists for Artweek and Artscene and other publications. Files also include exhibition announcements, artist resumes and biographical information, clippings, limited correspondence, and some photographs and negatives of artwork. Artists covered include Carlos Almarez, Larry Bell, Wallace Berman, Lorser Feitelson, Dan Flavin, Robert Graham, Jules Langsner, Rachel Rosenthal, Alexis Smith, and John White, among many others. There are also 4 sound cassettes of an interview with Richard Pettibone.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by artist name.
    - Akawie, Thomas, 1977-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Almaraz, Carlos, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Antin, Eleanor, 1983-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bell, Larry, 1964-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bell, Larry, 1964-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bell, Larry, 1964-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Berman, Wallace, 1971-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Brice, William, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Brigante, Nicholas P., 1975-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Caroompas, Carole, 1975-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Carson, Karen, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Clothier, Peter, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correia, Steven V., 1982-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - DeFrance, Jim, 1973-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Dill, Laddie John, 1973-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Farber, Manny, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Feitelson, Lorser, 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Gordon, Joni, 1970-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Graham, Robert, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Harden, Marvin, 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Henderson, Victor, 1976-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Herold, Rick, 1969-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Hill, Charles Christopher, 1976-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hueter, James, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Kazanjian, Milano, 1981-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - Langsner, Jules, circa 1970-circa1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Lloyd, Gary, 1975-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Longo, Robert, 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Mesches, Arnold, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Motherwell, Robert, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Orr, Eric, 1976-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Pettibone, Richard, 1981 May 14; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes duplicates; 2 Sound cassettes Includes paper notes with interview quotes originals (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      Access copies are available on 2 sound cassettes.
    - Pettibone, Shirley, 1966-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Pissarro, Camille, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Rizk, Ron, 1979-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Rosenthal, Rachel, 1981-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - Shafer, Phyllis, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Skuro, Leonard, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Alexis, 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
    - Sorenson, Don, 1975-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Von Euer, Judith, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - White, John, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
      - Correspondence and Printed Material, 1969-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
      - Baum Gallery essay for Images and Issues, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - "Performance" Essay for Barnsdall Park Exhibition Catalog, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Municipal Art Gallery Artweek Review, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Printed Material, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Wingo, Michael, 1976-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Woelffer, Emerson, 1969-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Zehr, Connier, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Zlotnick, Diana, 1971-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Exhibitions, 1962-1986; 1.2; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists of writings for exhibition catalogs and reviews. In addition to article and essay drafts, the folders also include notes and printed material such as press releases and clippings about the shows. Most of the exhibition titles were retained as folder headings since Danieli's reviews often were untitled. There is 1 sound cassette about Ceeje Gallery.
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - California State University Gallery, Abstraction in Los Angeles, 1950-1980 (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art, LeRoy Neiman and Andy Warhol Show (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - L.A. Louver, California: A Sense of Individualism (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles Valley College, Four Painters Show (1981), 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - ARCO Center for Visual Art, Plank House Architecture of the NW Coast Indians (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Beyond Baroque Foundation, Time Machine (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Young Talent (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Santa Barbara Contemporary Arts Forum, Black on Black (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Design Center of Los Angeles, A Broad Spectrum: Contemporary Los Angeles Painters and Sculptors (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles Municipal Art Gallery, Ceeje Revisited (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
      - Writings and Exhibition Catalogs, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Ceeje Gallery Interview with Jerry Jerome and Cecil Hendrick, 1983 October 29; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Printed Material, undated, 1962-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Fisher Art Gallery, California Sculpture Show (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles County Museum, A Day in the Country (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art, Automobile and Culture (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Newport Harbor Art Museum, California Art Since 1945 (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Writings, 1982-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Other Subjects, circa 1970-1986; 1.3; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists of writings and research on assorted subjects such as a special edition of Images and Issues magazine on L.A. artists, index cards of notes on the chronology of L.A. Art, and 4 sound cassettes of miscellaneous recordings including television episodes about art.
    Materials are grouped by medium or document type, then organized chronologically within each grouping. Drafts of writings come first, followed by index cards, then sound cassettes.
    - Artscene, "Writer's Recommendations", 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Images and Issues Edition on Los Angeles Artists in the 1960s, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1872-1920, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1920-1929, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1930s, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1940s, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1950s, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1960s, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Index Cards of L.A. Art Chronology, 1970-1975, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Index Cards on Renaissance Art, circa 1970-circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - NBC Speaking Freely Episode with Claude Levi-Strauss, 1974 January 20; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - NBC Speaking Freely Episode with John Cage and Merce Cunningham, 1974 June 9; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - NBC Tomorrow Episode with "Futurists" Panel, 1974 January 17; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Recording of Conversation with Unknown Artist, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Artist Interviews and Performances, 1974-1975; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 3.1 Linear feet Boxes 4-7
  There are duplicate access copies for a few of the cassettes.
  This series consists of 45 artist interviews, as well as recordings of performances and art talks dating from 1974-1975 on 108 sound cassettes, along with a few interview transcripts. The sound recordings appear to be part of the UCLA oral history project "LA Community Artists." Most of the cassettes are artist interviews conducted by Danieli, but there are also recordings of art talks, panel discussions, seminars, performances, and informal group discussions. Artists include David Antin, Eleanor Antin, Judith Bettelheim, Nick Brigante, Annita Delano, Allan Kaprow, Peter Krasnow, Peter Plagens, Gary Lloyd, John McLaughlin, Shirley Pettibone, Betye Saar, and John White, among many others.
  Several of the cassette tape containers have detailed handwritten labels that specify the location of the interview, the subject of discussion, and other information.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by artist. Recordings of events and group discussions are grouped together at the end of the series alphabetically by event title. For a later interview with the artist Richard Pettibone, and another recording about the Ceeje Gallery, see series 1, Writing and Research Files.
  - Anderson, Jerry, 1974 February 22; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Antin, David, 1974 May 16; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Antin, Eleanor, 1974 April 19; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Arnold, Florence, 1974 August 21; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Atlas, Jacoba, 1974 April 4; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bettelheim, Judith, 1974 February 28; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bettelheim, Judith, 1974 April 18; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bon-Bons, Jerry, 1974 February 4; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brigante, Nick, 1974 August 20; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brigante, Nick, 1975 January 28; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Brod, Michael, 1974 March 18; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Canavier, John, 1974 August 8; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Caroompas, Carole, 1974 April 8; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Clayson, Hollis, 1974 May 2; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Cole, Max, 1974 February 23; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Crouch, Dora, 1974 March 21; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Delano, Annita, 1974 June 16-July 28; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Delano, Annita, 1974 October 20; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Delano, Annita, 1975 March 27; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Delano, Annita, 1975 July 6; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Deutsch, Boris, 1974 August 18; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fiskin, Judy, 1974 April 5; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Gabrielson, Walter, 1974 February 21; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Glicksman, Hal, 1974 March 10; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Grieger, Scott, 1974 April 2; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Sam Hyde, 1975 July 24; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Helms, George, 1974 March 30; Archival Resource Key; 4 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Ianco-Starrels, Josine, 1975 June 21; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kaprow, Allan, 1974 August 16; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Knitig, Carl, 1974 June 13; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Krasnow, Peter, 1974 May 28; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Krasnow, Peter, 1974 July 18; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Krasnow, Peter, 1974 October 19; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Krasnow, Peter, 1975 March 26; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lloyd, Gary, 1974 February 18; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette duplicate; 3 Sound cassettes originals (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Access copy included for sound cassette 1 of 3.
  - Lloyd, Gary, 1974 March 10; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lodato, Peter, 1974 February 19; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mabry, John, 1974 February 11; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - McCollum, Allan, 1974 April 1; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - McLaughlin, John, 1974 March 5; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Interview transcript only.
  - Orr, Eric, 1974 June 6; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pettibone, Shirley, 1974 February 15; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes duplicates; 2 Sound cassettes originals (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Includes access copies of the original tapes.
  - Plagens, Peter, 1974 May 30; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Saar, Betye, 1974 September 11; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Schroeder, John, 1974 March 1; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Barbara, 1974 July 30; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Von Euer, Judith, 1974 June 1; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Wagner, Gordon, 1974 July 11; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Westcoast, Wanda, 1974 March 18; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - White, John, 1974 June 9; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - White, John, 1975 October 8; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Group Performances, Discussions, and Events, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Decca-Dance Dadacademy Awards, 1974 February 2; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes Poor sound quality especially at the beginning. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Duologue" Music Performance with Terry Fox and Tom Marioni, 1975 May 29-30; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Group Discussion of Artists on Teaching, 1974 September 8; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "L.A. Investment Philosophy" Seminar, 1974 March 28; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Panel discussion on L.A. art and architecture
- Printed Material, 1969-1985; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 7-9